When people talk about Modern C++,
当人们谈论现代 C+ + 时
they're often referring to the C++ 11 release,
它们通常是指 C++ 11 发行版
which introduced a whole range of new features into the programming language.
在编程语言中引入了一系列的新功能
Move semantics, variadic templates,
移动语义 可变模板
initializer lists, the auto keyword,
初始化程序列表 自动关键字
lambda expressions, null pointer,
lambda 表达式 空指针
constant expression, range-based four loops, and smart pointers,
常量表达式 基于范围的四环和智能指针
all came into the C++ programming language as part
都变成了 C++ 编程语言
of C++ 11 and changed the language dramatically.
C++ 11 改变了语言
C++ 14 was a relatively minor release,
C++ 14 是一个比较小的版本
and C++ 17 was a major release,
和 C++ 17 是一个主要的发行版
although not as big as the C++ 11 release.
虽然不像 C++ 11 发行版那么大
C++ 17 includes standard file system within the standard library,
C++ 17 包括标准库中的标准文件系统
standard string view, parallel implementations of
标准字符串视图 并行实现
many of the standard library algorithms, and inline variables.
许多标准库算法和内联变量
C++ 20 is scheduled as a minor release but will contain concepts
C++ 20 已调度为次要发行版 但将包含概念
which are an important tool for improving generic programming with templates in C++.
它是在 C++中使用模板改进通用编程的重要工具